cpanel.com 2010-04-09

# Privacy Policy - cPanel Inc.

## Corporate

This Privacy Policy applies to cpanel.net hosted Web sites.

## 1.0 cPanel Privacy Practices

## 1.1 Personal Information

As a world leader in web hosting administration software, cPanel understand your desire to protect personal information.

**What Information We Gather and Track**

We request personal information when you place an order, request a service, answer a survey, correspond with us or engage in certain other activities on our Web site. 

For example: 

1\. If you submit an order on-line with us, we will ask you for information necessary to complete the transaction - such as your name, address, and credit card number. 

2\. If you request technical support online, we will ask you for information necessary to complete the transaction - such as your name, email address, and information about your computer hardware, software and the nature of the problem you are experiencing. You make the decision whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the transaction.

**How We Use the Information We Gather and Track**

We use personally identifiable information in the following ways:

1\. To provide you with information about security alerts, product discounts, informative mailings, and policy changes; 

2\. To assist us in creating content that is relevant to you; 

3\. To provide you with special offers that may be of interest to you and to improve your experience on our Web site; 

4\. To assist us in creating better products and services to meet your needs; 

5\. To allow you to purchase and download products, obtain access to services or otherwise engage in activities you select; 

6\. To help you quickly find software, services or product information important to you.

**With Whom We May Share Your Information**

cPanel takes personal privacy seriously. While we may need to share your information with third parties, cPanel will share your information only with parties that require such information. An example of this is that we must share your credit card information with our credit card processor so you can place orders on our site. 

Information posted in public profiles (forums, manage2) is not considered private and is therefore not protected under this privacy policy.

## 1.2 Security and Quality of Personal Information

We have taken rigorous security measure to protect your personal information. These measures include technical and procedural steps to protect your data from misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, loss, alteration, or destruction. Credit card information is transmitted using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption. 

We make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to update or correct your personal information. If you believe that cPanel does not have your current personal information, you can update it at <http://www.cpanel.net/store/>.

## 1.3 Web Site Traffic

Through our various tracking methods discussed above, we may track domain names, IP addresses, and browser types from people who visit our site. We use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout cPanel�s Web site. Such information is not correlated with any personal information.

## 1.4 Links to Business Partner Sites

At the cPanel Web site, there are a number of links to companies with whom we have a relationship. cPanel is not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners. We encourage you to read their privacy statements, as they may differ from ours.

## 1.5 Other Privacy Considerations

Please remember that information you submit in a discussion group or forum, like the "cPanel Forums", will be deemed public information and is not confidential. There is a risk in such communication venues that information can be collected and used by others. Please be careful and responsible when you are online.

## 1.6 cPanel Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments concerning this policy, or if you would like update or review the personal information we have about you, or withdraw your consent for the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information, please contact us using one of the options below:

Customer Service Contact:

<https://tickets.cpanel.net/submit/index.cgi?reqtype=cs>

Postal Mail:  
cPanel Inc.  
ATTN: Privacy  
3701 Kirby Dr #428  
Houston, TX 77098   
Telephone 713-529-0800
